Ta Thanh Dat / Web Developer

Gender Male

Phone +84 374 098 439

Email Dattt229@gmail.com

Address Dong Da, Ha Noi

Website https://github.com/TaTaDa229



OBJECTIVE

Be looking forward to working in a professional, dynamic and challenging environment in order to improve knowledge and accumulate experiences.

Make the best effort to complete the assigned tasks and contribute to personal career as well as the development of company.

SKILLS

Front-end	HTML, CSS, SASS, Bootstrap, Javascript, ReactJS, SwiperJS
Back-end	NodeJS, ExpressJS, MongoDB
Tools	Git, Postman
English	Toeic 700+
Office	Word, Excel, Powerpoint
Soft skills	Teamwork, Self-study, Work hard, Work responsibility

EDUCATION

Feb 2022 - Aug 2022	MindX Technology School Major: Web Fullstack Second Prize of MindX's Hackathon
Jun 2013 - Jun 2017	Banking Academy Major: Finance & Banking Encouragement scholarships of Banking Academy.

ACTIVITIES

Apr 2016 - Apr 2017	Microsoft Office Specialist Team of Banking Academy Participant in Microsoft Office Specialist World Championship
May 2015 - May 2016	SvnhForum - The official Forum of Banking Academy Member of the Technical Team

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jun 2017 - Jun 2022	Asia Commercial Bank
Jun 2017 - Jun 2022	Asia Commerciai Bank

Officer of Customer Management Department

PROJECTS

BlogWebsite	 Technoligies: ReactJS, Boostrap, Material UI, Redux, NodeJS, MongoDB, ExpressJS, JWT Live demo: https://blog-website1.netlify.app/ Source code: https://github.com/TaTaDa229/BlogWebsite
PortfolioWebsite	Technoligies: ReactJS, EmailJS, SwiperLive demo: https://portfolio-website-dattt.vercel.app/Source code: https://github.com/TaTaDa229/Portfolio-Website
MusicPlayer	Technoligies: HTML, CSS, JavaScriptLive demo: https://tatada229.github.io/MusicPlayerSource code: https://github.com/TaTaDa229/MusicPlayer
CalculatorJS	Technoligies: HTML, CSS, JavaScriptLive demo: https://tatada229.github.io/CalculatorJS/Source code: https://github.com/TaTaDa229/CalculatorJS
ShopeeWeb	Technoligies: HTML, CSSLive demo: https://tatada229.github.io/ShopeeWeb/Source code: https://github.com/TaTaDa229/ShopeeWeb